[
   {
     "qno": 1,
"question": "What is the HCF of 18 and 24?",
"opa": "2",
"opb": "3",
"opc": "6",
"opd": "12",
"correctanswer": "3"
},
   {
     "qno": 2,
"question": "Which of the following is not a factor of 72?",
"opa": "9",
"opb": "6",
"opc": "8",
"opd": "11",
"correctanswer": "4"
},
   {
     "qno": 3,
"question": "What is the value of: 3² + 4²?",
"opa": "25",
"opb": "21",
"opc": "16",
"opd": "19",
"correctanswer": "1"
},
   {
     "qno": 4,
"question": "If 5 pencils cost ₹35, what is the cost of 12 pencils?",
"opa": "₹72",
"opb": "₹84",
"opc": "₹90",
"opd": "₹98",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
   {
     "qno": 5,
"question": "The sum of the angles in a triangle is:",
"opa": "90°",
"opb": "180°",
"opc": "270",
"opd": "360",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
   {
     "qno": 6,
"question": "Which is greater: 3/4 or 5/8?",
"opa": "3/4",
"opb": "5/8",
"opc": "Both are equal",
"opd": "Cannot be determined",
"correctanswer": "1"
},
   {
     "qno": 7,
"question": "Solve: (2 + 3) × (4 + 1) = ?",
"opa": "10",
"opb": "25",
"opc": "20",
"opd": "15",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
   {
     "qno": 8,
"question": "Find the missing number: 2, 6, 12, 20, __, 42",
"opa": "28",
"opb": "34",
"opc": "32",
"opd": "30",
"correctanswer": "4"
},
   {
     "qno": 9,
"question": "What is the smallest 4-digit number divisible by 3?",
"opa": "1008,
"opb": "1006",
"opc": "1002",
"opd": "1000",
"correctanswer": "3"
},
   {
     "qno": 10,
"question": "What is the largest 4-digit number divisible by 4?",
"opa": "9992",
"opb": "9996",
"opc": "9998",
"opd": "9999",
"correctanswer": "2"
}
]
